99localsearch.com 2018-09-15

# 99LocalSearch - Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy sets out our practices with respect to the personal information of our user. We collect, use and disclose personal information for the use of 99localsearch.com and keep it safe to our maximum extent. We utilize safe, secure technology to protect your personally identifiable information. We value your trust in us and will work hard to earn your confidence, so that you can enthusiastically use our services and recommend us to family and friends. This Privacy Policy may be updated by us at any time by posting on the site without any prior notice. Also, this Privacy Statement may be supplemented or modified by agreements entered into between us and an individual from time to time. 

#### Collection of Personal Information

We collect personally information such as name, email address and contact phone number while you post ad using our website. However, you understand that ad description and other contact information will be displayed on the website when other users view your ad details, and that our website pages may be linked by third party websites or search engines. You agree that we may send you email using your email address if provided when the users viewing your ad want to contact you by using our email system. 

#### Disclosure of Personal Information

We may disclose certain personal information as follows: 

  * By publishing ads either online and/or in print, as the case may be, in connection with items that are for sale by customers 
  * to third party service providers and to affiliated entities in order to carry out work on our behalf, 
  * to law enforcement agencies for the purposes of investigating fraud or other offences, or 
  * to legal, financial, and other professional advisors or in connection with the sale or reorganization of all or part of its business or operations. 
  * By having your mobile number listed on [99localsearch.com](http://www.99localsearch.com/), you agree to receive communication from third parties who may wish to contact you through the site. 

Except as provided above, we will not use or disclose personal information for purposes other than those for which it was collected, except with the consent of the individual or as required or permitted by law. 

#### Links

This Site contains links to other websites, such as websites providing national search capabilities and information resources designed to inform buyers and sellers about general aspects of property that is being sold. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. Please ensure you review the privacy policies of the websites that you visit. 

#### Security

We protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of personal information with security measures appropriate to the sensitivity of the information. However, it is possible that any information transmitted via the Internet may be intercepted by unknown third parties. We use Verisign to have credit card data transmitted to our network servers in a secure encrypted mode. 

#### Opt-Out

When appropriate, users of the Site are given the opportunity to (i) opt-out of receiving communications from us, (ii) remove their information from our database, or (iii) elect to no longer receive services from us. If you wish to opt-out of receiving further communications, please contact us. 

#### Corrections/Contact

Users of this Site may contact 99localsearch to modify or correct any of their personal information that is under our control. An individual may also direct a written complaint regarding compliance with this Privacy Statement to us and, within a reasonable time upon receiving the written complaint, we will conduct an investigation into the matter, and we will take necessary measure/s to rectify the source of the complaint, as appropriate. 

#### Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement, our privacy practices in connection with this Site, or our collection, use, disclosure, or retention of your personal information in connection with this Site, please contact us at [info@99localsearch.com](mailto:info@99localsearch.com)
